outshinesolutions.com 2019-03-09

# Privacy Policy - Outshine Solutions Pvt. Ltd.

**What This Privacy Policy Covers**

This policy covers how Outshine Solutions treats personal information that Outshine Solutions collects and receives, including information related to your past use of Outshine Solutions products and services, your use of www.Outshinesolutions.com, www.Outshinesolution.com and/or any Outshine Solutions web sites. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.

**Clients**  
Outshine Solutions services and products are developed for the use of, and distributed to, third party clients. Outshine Solutions encourages its clients to adopt privacy policies similar to, or more stringent than, its own. Outshine Solutions sells its services and products only to reputable and ethical clients. Outshine Solutions cannot be held responsible if a client chooses unethical or immoral use of the information that the Outshine Solutions products gather.

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Outshine Solutions does not own or control, or to people that Outshine Solutions does not employ or manage.

**Information Collection and Use**

When you register for a Outshine Solutions event or services, we ask that you provide basic contact information such as your name, address, and email address. In addition, other questions specifically for an event might be asked and recorded so as to better equip the event hosts for customizing their event.

Upon successful registration, you automatically opt in for Outshine Solutions service communications, as specified on the Web form.

Outshine Solutions collects personal information when you register with Outshine Solutions, when you use Outshine Solution products or services, when you visit Outshine Solutions pages or the pages of certain Outshine Solutions partners, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. Outshine Solutions may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.

Outshine Solutions automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, Outshine Solutions cookie information, and the page you request.

Outshine Solutions uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. Information Collected Automatically We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us via Outshinesolutions.com.

**Computer configuration** : We automatically receive and log information from your browser, including your IP address, browser type and version,  and connection speed.

**Referral,   and site interaction data**: We may also record the URL you linked from to get to Outshinesolutions.com,  through and from our Web site, and other generally accepted tracking information.

**Email delivery and open rates:** To help us make our emails more useful and interesting, and to ensure that we are delivering the services you have ordered, we often receive a confirmation when you receive and/or open email from Outshinesolutions.com

**Information Sharing and Disclosure  
**  
Outshine Solutions does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non affiliated companies except to provide products or services you’ve requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

Trusted third parties: With your consent, we will make your Personal Information available to trusted third parties who offer products and services we think may be of interest to you so that you can receive information or opportunities related to those products and services. A trusted third party may use shared information in accordance with its own privacy policy ; We transfer information about you if Outshine Solutions is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Outshine Solutions will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

Outshine Solutions displays targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click on targeted ads meet the targeting criteria – for example, women ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area. o Outshine Solutions does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad. Email Communications to our Users Outshine Solutions sends email communications to our users in connection with our providing the Outshine Solution services. The following outlines the types of email Outshine Solutions sends to our users, and the choices you have about which messages to receive.

Messages required to service event registrations: Outshine Solutions will send you email notifying you of your event details. We may also send you communications related to your upcoming event, for example reminding you of the details, or when those details change.

Messages required to service your Outshine Solutions account: Outshine Solutions may send newly registered users a welcoming email, as well as messages confirming each event you register for at Outshine Solutions.com; confirming your account changes; inviting you to participate in customer surveys; and informing you of important product or service updates related to our core business.

Marketing messages about Outshine Solutions: We may send you marketing messages related to our services you receive, for example, encouraging you to register for more Webinars or extend your Web event presence.

Optional marketing messages from Outshine Solutions: Registered users may also occasionally receive information or special promotions from Outshine Solutions about additional services. You may update your preference with regard to receiving such messages by opting out in the footer of each email.

Optional marketing messages from trusted third parties: With your consent, Outshine Solutions may share your Personal Information with trusted third parties so that you may receive information or opportunities from them about relevant products and services they offer. You may update your preference by opting out in the footer of each email.

**Cookies**

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that a Web site can store on your computer’s hard drive. When you visit Outshine Solutions.com, create a user account, or otherwise interact with a Outshine event online, we may set cookies on your personal computer. We require that cookies be enabled in your Web browser so that we can identify you as a repeat visitor or customer and maintain session information for logged-in users. We also use cookies to track usage trends and patterns in order to better understand and improve areas of our Web site. Outshine Solutions may allow other companies that are providing content on our site to set and access their own cookies on your computer. Other companies’ use of cookies is subject to their respective privacy policies.

Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences.

We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the Outshine Solutions service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the Outshine Solutions Newsletter, that are considered part of your Outshine Solutions account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them.

**Confidentiality and Security**

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you.

‘No Spyware’ Policy

Outshine Solutions does not contain Spyware. Spyware is software that is installed deceptively to gather information about you without your knowledge. This can include centrally recording your personal internet usage, monitoring your keyboard strokes or capturing personal information. If you think that you downloaded and/or installed spyware, we suggest reporting it on the alt.privacy.spyware newsgroup. Available on Google Groups.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Outshine Solutions may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Outshine Solutions account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

**Questions and Suggestions**

If you have questions or suggestions, please use the [contact information to contact us](http://outshinesolutions.com/contact-us/ "Contact Outshine Solutions").
